Sir first start with HDFC Live.
Yes, no, you should start from where you are live.
Ok buy it for around ₹750
as many people are
getting bad results.  A
is slightly less than expected.   It is not that it is not there.
But I
believe that take it around yesterday's low of 750 748.
Place a stop loss of 740
or else you have the option of 748.
Either place a straight stop loss of 748
and buy or buy around 750 and
place a stop loss of 740.  Ok
?  765 771 780
is a slightly weaker rate for targets.  As expected
but VNB growth looks quite good to
me.  If margin improvement is
visible in all segments then it is fine.  The
biggest thing that the management gave guidance was that
second H2 should be more than H1, now you should speak,
Anil ji these days have started speaking like all the English
people,
first half and second half,
yes I will teach you,
because ultimately see what it is, once
you learn it, then nothing is difficult,
understand a little bit of this business language
every day, h2 means what, second half of the year,
second half, yes
second half,
correct
h1 first half, now the first half of the year
is which financial year?  From April to
September.
Correct.
Now HDFC Life said that our second half will be
better.  That is, the time from October to
March.  The period from October 2025 to March 26 will be
much better and the
market is enjoying it.  Wow Vibha Padalkar ji
very nice.  You gave a good outlook.
Vibha Padalkar ji, I will tell her MD.
Then he will say who is this if you ask.
Yes.  So he has given a very good statement
and after seeing it people feel
that it should be good.  And
two or three brokerages announced price targets today.  The
excerpts are telling.  Ready at the top,
Ansh is the same, right? Today it will be HDFC Life only.
Yes, I know, after seeing it I felt that this could be an
opportunity for you to buy HDFC Life.
ICIC LBARD: Note the support level
around 1945.  2055 is the upper level.
Ok?  The results are looking good.  HD
HDFC L is not as bad as it looks.
And the ICIC Low L is not as good as it looks.   It
is important to look inside.  Meaning it
is not bad but not that good.   The
difference between the two makes the
environment a bit difficult for the entire industry.   He
gave good results in that.
Ok.  Better than others.
Profit is as expected.  But
their GDP growth is a bit slow.
Meaning, I did not enjoy it as much as I should have.
Still, earnings estimates may increase slightly by 1 to 2%.
So
if you find it near the support level then buy it.   If it
crosses and stays above 205, then you
should think that now the result discount that was to be given to it has been done,
after that it will increase rapidly.
So comfortably the third one is another cash result
that I want to discuss and that is
HDB finance which is the first result after listing.  I didn't
enjoy it.
Well, revenue increased by 18% but profits declined by 2%.   It
is a HDFC Group company.  The result is the
first result after the listing.
I don't expect that.  Didn't enjoy it.  I have seen very weak
results.  Perhaps the vehicle financing
business did not do very well.
Let's see what the management says.   The
thing is that the kind of response we got and the
results are nowhere near what we expected.
Dooroor means very far
from what one expects, that's all.
Ok.  Okay, this is the result review
but now Bigul Stock of
Ah No Waji